// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "?",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "",
    answer: "",
    options: [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ]
  },

];
let MusicQuestions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What was Fontaines DC's debut album?",
    answer: "Dogrel",
    options: [
      "Dogrel",
      "A Hero's Death",
      "Skinty  Fia",
      "Couldn't tell ye mate"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which Stanglers album contained the single: Golden Brown",
    answer: "La Folie",
    options: [
      "No more Heroes",
      "La Folie",
      "Black and White",
      "Dreamtime"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is the frontman of the strokes",
    answer: "Julian Casablancas",
    options: [
      "Joe McDonnel",
      "Patsy V",
      "Julian Casablancas",
      "Ted Sharkey"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What year was Bobby Womack's Across 110th Street released",
    answer: "1973",
    options: [
      "1916",
      "1981",
      "1962",
      "1973"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Bicep are from what Irish city?",
    answer: "Belfast",
    options: [
      "Derry",
      "Belfast",
      "Dublin",
      "Cork"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];

let MovieQuestions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which of the following is not a film directed by Martin McDonagh ",
    answer: "The Guard",
    options: [
      "The Guard",
      "In Bruges",
      "Three Billboards",
	  "Seven Psychopaths"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "In what year was Goodfellas released?",
    answer: "1990",
    options: [
      "1985",
      "2001",
      "1990",
      "2026"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who directed Se7en",
    answer: "David Fincher",
    options: [
      "David lynch",
      "Paul Giamtti",
      "David Fincher",
      "Ed wood"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "what is the name of the character played by Christoph Waltz in Django Unchained",
    answer: "King Schultz",
    options: [
      "Django",
      "Hans Landa",
      "King Schultz",
      "Mr Teeth"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Did ye see that film with yer man in it?",
    answer: "what are you doing in my house?",
    options: [
      "Sir, I am blind.",
      "No",
      "Yes",
      "What are you doing in my house?"
    ]
  },

];let TVQuestions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Is there a man staring at you with a T-Shirt saying I sahot JR",
    answer: "BIRD!!",
    options: [
      "oh aye",
      "No",
      "What",
	  "BIRD!!"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "How many series of Breaking Bad were there?",
    answer: "5",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "5",
      "32"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Where was kings road in Game of thrones Filmed",
    answer: "The Dark Hedges",
    options: [
      "Giants Causeway",
      "the M12",
      "The Dark Hedges",
      "Green screen"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "How many Doctors have their been in doctor who?",
    answer: "13",
    options: [
      "19",
      "7",
      "21",
      "13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How is Danny Dyer still on TV?",
    answer: "Pact with satan",
    options: [
      "Talent",
      "He knows where the bodies are buried",
      "Pact with satan",
      "Yes"
    ]
  },

];
